lovevoodoo.com 2015-12-07

# LoveVoodoo.com Privacy Statement

LoveVoodoo Privacy Statement

We at LoveVoodoo.com understand that your privacy is very important to you. That's why we've developed this policy to ensure that your privacy is protected while using our site.

A Special Note About Children   
About LoveVoodoo.com and Information We Collect   
Our Use of Your Information   
Our Disclosure of Your Information   
Your use of Other Users' Information   
Control of Your Password   
Reviewing and Changing Your Personally Identifiable Information   
Third Party Collections of Information  
Security  
Update/Delete 

A Special Note About Children  
Children under eighteen years of age are not eligible to use our services. We ask that children not submit information to us. 

About LoveVoodoo.com and Information We Collect  
LoveVoodoo.com is an online service which provides you useful tools and communities to build relationships online. 

In our online ANONYMOUS registration form, we ask you to provide us with certain information such as your age and the type of relationship you are looking for. However, NONE of the personally identifiable information can be accessed or used by the public to identify a specific individual. 

In the course of using our site, we automatically track certain information such as your IP addresses and email addresses. Many sites automatically collect this information. If you choose to post messages in our Events & Opportunities section, chat rooms, or other message areas, we will only display such information about you as you choose to reveal. 

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the site, we may collect such information into a file which is only accessed by authorized personnel. We may also collect other users' comments about you in our complaints department. 

Our Use of Your Information  
We internally use personally identifiable information of our users to improve our marketing efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings as well as to customize our site's content and layout. We believe these uses allow us to improve our site and better tailor your online experience to meet your needs. 

We may also use personally identifiable information about you to deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banners and promotions. 

We also send periodic informational updates to our members via email. 

We use personally identifiable information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our User Agreement. 

Our Disclosure of Your Information  
We DO NOT sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party without your permission. We do disclose information in aggregate to advertisers and for other marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we DO NOT disclose to these entities any information that could be used to personally identify you. Certain information, such as your password, credit card number, and bank account number, are not disclosed in aggregate at all. 

In order to maintain a healthy community, LoveVoodoo.com cooperates with all law enforcement inquiries and with all third parties to enforce their intellectual property or other rights. 

LoveVoodoo.com and our users do not tolerate spam, harassment, or threats. 

Control of Your Password  
You may not disclose your password to any third parties or share it with any third parties. If, despite the foregoing, you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password. 

Reviewing and Changing Your Personally Identifiable Information  
Once you register, you will be able to review and change much of your personally identifiable information at LoveVoodoo.com including: 

Your email address  
Your city, state, zip code, country  
Your password  
Your profile

Please promptly update your information if it changes.   

Third Party Collections of Information  
Our policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties on our system or other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the personal information you disclose to them. While LoveVoodoo.com is working closely with our partners to ensure the highest privacy to you, we encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others. 

Security  
LoveVoodoo.com has security measures in place to protect and prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. LoveVoodoo.com uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information such as firewalls. While "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet, our technical experts at LoveVoodoo.com work hard to ensure your secure use of our services. 

Update/Delete  
LoveVoodoo.com Members have the following choices to modify or delete their information from our database:

Send an email to our customer service rep. at info@LoveVoodoo.com or call 1 (866) 408-1369;

Log in with your password and modify your profile;

Send a snail mail to LoveVoodoo.com at Social Media Marketing, P.O. Box 262, Kenner, LA 70063 

\--------------------------  
Updated July, 2003
